RESUME

Jitendra H. Kasvala jitendra1202msw@gmail.com 8866268184

PROFILE SUMMARY:

Master of Social Work with 6+ years experience in serving the community. Experience in Government, Non-Government Organization and currently working in MAHSR Bullet Train Project, (National High Speed Rail Corporation Ltd). Seeking the opportunity to utilize my skills as an experienced Administration Assistant as well as Community Representative while helping company excel and meet long-term goals.

EDUCATIONAL DETAILS:

DEGREE	COLLEGE / UNIVERSITY	YEAR OF PASSING	PERCENTAGE
MSW	Gujarat University	2015	59.5
B. Com	Gujarat University	2013	59.78
HSC	GSEB	2010	58
SSC	GSEB	2006	50

WORK EXPERIENCE:

- 1. Worked with MDS Facilities as a Community representative in NHSRCL Vadodara (Bullet train project).
 - Worked in Project NHSRCL Mumbai-Ahmedabad High Speed Rail Project, supporting Resettlement and Rehabilitation work with implementing agency NHSRCL (Bullet train project), Started from February - 2019 till March 2021.

Currently working with Godawari Farms & Services as a Community representative in NHSRCL Vadodara (Bullet train project). April – 2021 till present

- Working in Project NHSRCL Mumbai-Ahmedabad High Speed Rail Project, supporting Resettlement and Rehabilitation work with implementing agency NHSRCL (Bullet train project)
 - a. Land Acquisition
 - b. Coordination with PAPs (Project Affected Person) Explaining Consent benefits.
 - c. Data updation, Pre-consent and organize consent camps.
 - d. Attending joint inspection/ verifications.
 - e. Regular Field visits for verification of acquired land.
 - f. Coordination with various government departments.
 - g. Prepare consent agreement and submit to head office

- 2. Worked with Saath Charitable Trust (NGO), Started from August 2016.
 - a. Project Grihaparvesh (August -2016 to January 2018) as a filed officer
 - Counselling of affordable scheme to clients/customers
 - b. Worked in Project MEGA as a field officer, Ahmedabad Gandhinagar Metro Rail Project, supporting Resettlement and Rehabilitation work with implementing agency MEGA, Started from January 2018 till January 2019.
 - Land Acquisition
 - SIA (Social impact assessment) form fill up with (GIDR) Gujarat institute of Development Research for the sensitive areas
 - Verification of SIA form and provide information to PAPs regarding required documents
 - Coordination with PAPs (Project Affected Person) Explaining benefits
 - Data updation, pre-meeting and organize meeting with implementing agency MEGA office
 - Attending joint inspection / verifications
 - Regular Field visits for verification of acquired land
 - Coordination with various government departments
 - Prepare PAPs documents and submit to implementing agency MEGA office
- **3. Dinbandhu Youth Welfare Trust** (A-301 Arsi corner, Opp. Gujarat College, Ellis Bridge, Ahmedabad-380006) **4 Month HIV/AIDS (TI Project)**.

PROJECT DETAILS:

A study on problem of severe diseases in the slums of Ahmedabad city

Diseases : Malaria / Chikungunia / Dengue

Information Gathered: History of disease / Causes of disease

Characteristic of Disease / Preventions of disease

Social and Economic effect of disease

Certifications: Basic Computer Course (MS Office)

SOCIAL WORK INTERNS

Community Work (Odhav): 6th August, 2013 to 29th October, 2013

- Two days (Tuesday & Thursday) in week.
- Community Work, Group Work, Case Study

Rukshmaniben Hospital (Maninagar): 24th December, 2013 to 18th February, 2014

- Two days (Tuesday & Thursday) in week.
- Information about HIV / AIDS, Sexual Disease

B. M Institute of Mental Health (Gandhi Gram Railway Station) 20th Feb, 2014 to 3rd April, 2014

- Two days (Tuesday & Thursday) in week.
- Working Mental disorder children

Mission Mangalam Scheme

Gujarat Livelihood Promotion Company Limited:1st July, 2014 to 15th October 2014

- Scheme Mission Mangalam functioning under District Rural Development Agency Gandhinagar.
- Topic Study for the Trainee was in Microfinance Sector in DehgamTaluka.

Personal details:

Name Jitendra H Kasvala

DOB 12th February, 1991

Sex Male

Address B1-703, Kesar Vatika,

Bh. Somnath Party Plot, Nr. Fortune Sky Mall,

Nikol, Ahmedabad - 382350.

Languages KnownEnglish, Hindi, Gujarati

Hobbies Movies, travelling, Listening Songs

Strength Hardworking, self motivator and good team player

Declaration: I, Jitendra H Kasvala hereby declare that the information mentioned in the resume is trueand best to my knowledge.

Place: Ahmedabad Jitendra H. Kasvala